Hey guys, welcome back. Now, if you have
truly finished all the hands-on, and if
you are here after replicating what I've done so far
in this project, give yourself a pat on the back, because
not many do this. So you really deserve the
appreciation. So I really congratulate you for
having done the hands-on with me.
Okay? Now, the project is not done yet.
We still have to learn about
concepts such as S3 event-driven
orchestration, and the more important topics
such as performance optimization and cost optimizations,
okay? You'll also have to learn about how do you save money from
the S3 storage perspective, okay?
All of these topics are covered in the next course, From
Average to Highly Paid. Okay, so if you have done
all of the hands-on so far, and if you've also gone through the deep dive course,
which was a parallel to this course, right?
You should have done that course as well to, to get some additional
knowledge about, you know, what the, the, the hands-on you've been doing in
this course. And if you have finished these two,
go straight to the course From Average
to Highly Paid. And that course not just talks about these additional
skills I just mentioned, but that course will open up your
mind towards what is really possible if you gain
additional skills such as lakehouse engineering, big data engineering using
Apache Spark, data warehousing, CICD,
a lot more stuffs. Okay? So don't miss that course.
That is extremely important. And again, I want to really
congratulate you for having done the hands-on with
me. You now have the power to really
change your life. Trust me when I say this, because
not easily you get
a full-fledged, real project given to you on a platter,
okay? All you got to do
is really replicate me. Even in the next course, Performance Optimization,
that is a very, very critical segment, okay?
You will have to go through that content at least two, one to three times
to truly grasp the importance and truly
grasp, you know, um, I would say, the
depth of what has been covered over there.
And if you are really able to replicate in the
interview, you know, what you would be doing by looking
at my videos,
then you will do very well in the interviews, and I can
tell you that confidently. Okay? So I'll see you in the next course,
and, uh, if you have found this entire course
really, really beneficial, if it was very, very
insightful, then let me know in the comment below that
you really found it useful, and
you really think that it can truly change your
life. Okay? I'll talk to you soon.